Guide to the Azalea Society of America Records
Azalea Society of America Records
- Chapters, 1980-2006; 1980 2006; 1.25 linear feet
  - Robert D. Gartrell. Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Survey. Chapter Activities (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Tri-State (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Tri-State. Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Vaseyi (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Vaseyi. Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Vaseyi. Chapter Administration, 2005-2006 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Vaseyi. Chapter News Clippings, 2000-2005 (Flatfile 4)
  - Vaseyi. Press Clippings, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1954-2005; 1954 2005; 3.5 linear feet
  Correspondence includes memoranda and electronic mail as well as postal mail sent to and from the Azalea Society of America. Correspondence is arranged chronologically. Although some correspondence related to the society's journal, The Azalean may be found in this series, most correspondence directly related to the publication and distribution of The Azalean will be found in Series 6. The early correspondence in this series is chiefly correspondence among members of the Board of Governors concerning creation and amendments of the bylaws, incorporation of the society, formation of chapters, and the society's tax status. Throughout this series there are letters and memoranda about annual meetings, the society's finances, and membership. Also included are letters inquiring about membership in the society or requesting information about azaleas. Frequent correspondents are Ryon Page, William C. Miller, Robert Hobbs, Bob Stelloh, and William B. McIntosh.
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1954, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1984. [no month], Jan-Jun (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1986. Jan-Apr (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1986. May-Jun (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1986. Jul-Dec (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1987. Jan-Apr (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1984. Jul-Dec (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1987. May-Aug (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1987. Sep-Dec (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1988. Mar-Apr (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1988. [no month], Jan-Feb (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1988. May (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1988. Jun (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1988. Sep (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1988. Jul-Aug (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1988. Oct (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1988. Nov (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1988. Dec (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1989. [no month], Jan (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1989. Feb (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1989. Mar (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1989. Apr (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1989. May-Jun (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1989. Jul-Oct (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1989. Nov-Dec (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1990. [no month], Jan (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1990. Feb (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1990. Mar-Apr (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1990. May-Jun (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1990. Jul-Sep (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1990. Oct (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1990. Nov-Dec (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1991. [no month], Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1991. Mar-Apr (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1991. May-Sep (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1991. Oct-Dec (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1992. [no month], Jan-Mar (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1992. Apr-Jun (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1992. Jul-Dec (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1994. [no month], Jan-Jun (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1994. Jul-Aug (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1994. Sep-Dec (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1995. Jan-Mar (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1995. Apr-Jun (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1995. Jul-Dec (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1996. Jan-Mar (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1996. Apr-Jun (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1996. Jul-Aug (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1996. Sep-Oct (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1996. Nov-Dec (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1997. [no month] (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1997. Jan (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1997. Feb (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1997. Mar-Apr (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1997. May (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1997. Jun (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1997. Jul (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1997. Aug (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1997. Sep (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1997. Oct (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1997. Nov (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1997. Dec (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1998. [no month], Jan-Feb (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1998. Mar (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1998. Apr-May (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1998. Jun-Jul (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1998. Aug-Sep (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1998. Oct-Dec (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1999. [no month], Jan-Feb (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1999. Mar (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1999. Apr-Jun (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1999. Jul (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1999. Aug (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1999. Sep-Dec (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 2000. Jan-Jun (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1990-2006 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence undated, 1977-2006 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - American Rhododendron Society mailing labels, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - American Rhododendron Society membership lists, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Members, 1977-2008; 1977 2008; 3.25 linear feet
  This series contains materials related to the members of the Azalea Society of America. Members are broken down into groups: annual members, life members, new members, and overseas members. Also included are lists of members, membership rosters, and various types of reports about members. Correspondence to the Azalea Society of America asking for information to join and information about paying annual dues can be found in the Correspondence series.
  The term "posting group" refers to accumulated member changes entered into the society's database at one time. The treasurer accumulated member renewals and new member applications until month-end or until he received thirty or forty of them and then posted them into the database at one sitting, thus creating "posting groups." He then printed some reports about the group.
  - Annual Members, 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Arthur Stubbs Memorial Service October 12, 2002 (Cardbox 62, Folder 1)
  - Arthus Leisk Stubbs Memorial, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Mailing Labels (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Mailing labels, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Mailing Lists (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Member dues information, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Member roster, 1996-1998 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Membership Committee, 1986-2006 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Membership Drops, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Membership Lists (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Membership Rosters, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Membership Rosters, 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Membership Rosters, 1981-1982 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Membership Rosters, 1986-1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Membership Rosters, 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Membership Rosters, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Membership Rosters, 1996-2000 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Membership Rosters, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Membership Roster, 2007-2008 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Membership Rosters. Design and Layout (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - New Members. Welcome Packet (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Obituaries (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Original Membership Records. Part A (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Original Membership Records. Part B (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Overseas (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Posting Groups, 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Posting Groups 3, 7-8, 10, 13-17, 21 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Posting Groups 405-417 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Posting Groups 504-505 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Posting Groups 71-74 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Posting Groups 710-712, 714 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Posting Groups 75-79 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Posting Groups 81-85 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Posting Groups 810-812 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Posting Groups 813-816 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Posting Groups 817-819 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Posting Groups 820-823 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Posting Groups 86-89, 91 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Posting Groups 904-925 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Posting Groups 981-989 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Posting Groups 9810-9815 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Posting Groups 9901-9904 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Posting Groups 818, 821, 987, and 988, 1998 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Posting Group 901-907, 1998-1999 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Posting Group 905-916, 1999 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Posting Group 917-925, 1999 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Posting Group 001-010, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Posting Group 011-019, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Posting Group 020-025, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Posting Group 101-108, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Posting Group 109-121, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Posting Group 122-127, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Posting Group 201-212, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Posting Group 213-222, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Posting Group 301-310 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Posting Group 311, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Posting Group 401-405, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Posting Group 406-419, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Posting Group 501-506, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Posting Group 507-519, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Posting Group 601-610, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Posting Group 612-622, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Posting Group 701-714, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Posting Groups. Multiple Groups (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Posting Groups, Various, 2006-2007 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Potential Members List, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Reports. Life Members (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Reports. Members by Chapter (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Reports. Membership Analysis (Halfbox 17, Folder 1)
  - Reports. Membership Charts (Halfbox 17, Folder 2)
  - Reports. Membership Renewals (Halfbox 17, Folder 3)
  - Reports. Membership Resignations (Halfbox 17, Folder 4)
  - Reports. Name and Address Changes (Halfbox 17, Folder 5)
  - Reports. New Members (Halfbox 17, Folder 6)
  - Reports. Non-Renewed Members (Halfbox 17, Folder 7)
  - Reports. Prepaid Members (Halfbox 17, Folder 8)
  - Reports. Status by Affiliation, 1996 (Halfbox 17, Folder 9)
  - Reports. Status by Affiliation, 1997 (Halfbox 17, Folder 10)
  - Reports. Status by Affiliation, 1998 (Halfbox 17, Folder 11)
  - Reports. Status by Affiliation, 1999 (Halfbox 17, Folder 12)
  - Reports. Status by Affiliation, 2000 (Halfbox 17, Folder 13)
  - Reports. Status by Affiliation, 2004 (Halfbox 17, Folder 14)
- Photographs, 2000-2005, undated; 2000 2005; 0.5 linear feet
  This series consists of photographs related to the Azalea Society of America. Included in this series are about seventy photographs and six 35mm negatives of people, landscapes, and plants. People present include: Fred Galle, Betty Galle, George Harding, Joan Lerner, Milt Lerner, Ryon Page, Faith Page, and Ed Collins. Some photographs were taken at the 1990 Brookside Azalea Sale.
  - Bay Country azalea photos. Item MC00348CD004, 2000-2005 (Cardbox 62, Folder 4)
  - Digital photos by David Royster. Item MC00348CD005, 2000-2005 (Cardbox 62, Folder 5)
  - Film canister seedlings series, unknown (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Landscape, 1993 (Halfbox 17, Folder 15)
    This folder contains 24 3x5 photographic prints of a landscape. These prints were produced in 1993.
  - Logos (Halfbox 17, Folder 16)
  - Negatives (Halfbox 17, Folder 17)
    This folder contains six 35mm negatives of Fred and Betty Galle planting azaleas outside a house in December 1995. Prints of four of these images can be found in the Photographs: People folder, Folder 18 in Half Box 17.
  - People, 1986-1995 and undated (Halfbox 17, Folder 18)
    This folder contains 40 photographs (3x5, 4x6, and 5x7 prints). Most are identified and dated on the verso side. People present include: Fred Galle, Betty Galle, Bob Stewart, Nancy Swell, George Harding, Joan Lerner, Milt Lerner, Sue Switzer, George Switzer, Margaret Church, Tony Dove, Della Dove, Bobby Jones, Joe Blackwell, Philabell Blackwell, Ryon Page, Faith Page, Ed Roth, Thais Spencer, Bob Stelloh, Weldon Delp, and Ed Collins. Some photographs were taken at the Brookside Azalea Sale of 1990.
  - Plants (Halfbox 17, Folder 19)
    This folder contains three items: 4x6 photographic prints of an azalea and a rhododendron luteum, and a drawing of a bonsai.
  - University of Minnesota azalea photos. Item MC00348CD001, 2004 (Cardbox 62, Folder 1)
  - University of Minnesota azalea photos. Item MC00348CD002, 2004 (Cardbox 62, Folder 2)
  - University of Minnesota azalea photos. Item MC00348CD003, 2004 (Cardbox 62, Folder 3)
- Publications, 1933-2013; 1933 2013; 25.77 linear feet
  The Publications series contains three subseries: The Azalean, Other Publications of the Azalea Society of America, and Publications of Other Organizations. The first and largest subseries consists of issues of the journal of the Azalea Society of America, The Azalean, and related material. The issue production files contain correspondence related to The Azalean, as well as draft copies of articles and other material used in publishing each issue. The second subseries contains newsletters of the various chapters of the society and brochures distributed by the Azalea Society of America. The last subseries contains publications of other organizations.
  - The Azalean, 1979-2009
    - Ad checks, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Ad media kit, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Article drafts submitted or printed in Azalean, 1976-1991 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Azalean ad invoices, 1992-1994 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Azalean ad invoices, 1995-1999 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Azalean ad invoices, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Azalean ad invoices, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Azalean ad invoices, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Azalean articles for reprint, 1988-1989 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Azalean artwork, 1979-2005 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Azalean ASA addresses for mailing, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Azalean back issue index, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Azalean costs and expenses, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Azalean drafts, 1993 (Legalbox 61, Folder 4)
    - Azalean Executive Committee, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Azalean filler, 1978-1996 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Azalean forms, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Azalean inventory of back issues, 1991-1993 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Azalean Landon ads, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Azalean production invoices, 1991-1995 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Azalean production quotes and information, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Azalean production style guide, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Azalean promotions poster Insect and Mite Pests, 1979-2005 (Flatfile 1)
    - Azalean roundtable ideas, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Azalean roundtable ideas, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Azalean article drafts, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Best article ballot, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Best article ballot, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Best article certificate, 1990-1998 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Columbia Nursery Newsletter, 1969-1974 (Legalbox 61, Folder 2)
    - Expenses and bank statement, 1997-1999 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Gardening Know-How Magazine, 1997 (Legalbox 61, Folder 3)
    - Index for photographs by Ray Charles Phillips, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - ISSN Receipt, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 7 No. 1, 1985 March (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 10 No. 1, 1988 March (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 10 No. 3 (1 of 5), 1988 September (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 10 No. 3 (2 of 5), 1988 September (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 10 No. 3 (3 of 5), 1988 September (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 10 No. 3 (4 of 5), 1988 September (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 10 No. 1 (5 of 5), 1988 September (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 1 (1 of 4), 1989 March (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 1 (2 of 4), 1989 March (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 1 (3 of 4), 1989 March (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 1 (4 of 4), 1989 March (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 2 (1 of 4), 1989 June (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 2 (2 of 4), 1989 June (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 2 (3 of 4), 1989 June (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 2 (4 of 4), 1989 June (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 2. Articles, 1989 June (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 2. Correspondence, 1989 June (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 2. Publication Information, 1989 June (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 3 (1 of 4), 1989 September (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 3 (2 of 4), 1989 September (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 3.(3 of 4), 1989 September (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 3 (4 of 4), 1989 September (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 4, 1989 December (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 4. Articles, 1989 December (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 4. Correspondence, 1989 December (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 4. Photographs, 1989 December (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 11 No. 4. Publication Information, 1989 December (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 1, 1990 March (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 1. Correspondence, 1990 March (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 1. Photographs, 1990 March (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 1. Publication, 1990 March (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 2, 1990 June (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 2. Art Copy, 1990 June (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 2. Articles, 1990 June (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 2. Correspondence, 1990 June (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 2. Publication Information, 1990 June (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 3, 1990 September (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 3. Articles, 1990 September (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 3. Correspondence, 1990 September (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 3. Photographs, 1990 September (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 3. Publication Information, 1990 September (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 4, 1990 December (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 4. Articles, 1990 December (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 4. Correspondence, 1990 December (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 12 No. 4. Publication Information, 1990 December (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 1, 1991 March (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 1. Advertisers, 1991 March (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 1. Articles, 1991 March (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 1. Correspondence, 1991 March (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 1. Publication Information, 1991 March (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 2, 1991 June (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 2. Articles, 1991 June (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 2. Correspondence, 1991 June (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 2. Publication Information, 1991 June (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 3 (1 of 3), 1991 September (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 3 (2 of 3), 1991 September (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 3 (3 of 3), 1991 September (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 4, 1991 December (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 4. Articles, 1991 December (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 4. Correspondence, 1991 December (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 13 No. 4. Publication Information, 1991 December (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 1 (1 of 5), 1992 March (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 1 (2 of 5), 1992 March (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 1 (3 of 5), 1992 March (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 1 (4 of 5), 1992 March (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 1 (5 of 5), 1992 March (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 2 (1 of 3), 1992 June (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 2 (2 of 3), 1992 June (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 2 (3 of 3), 1992 June (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 3 (1 of 3), 1992 September (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 3 (2 of 3), 1992 September (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 3 (3 of 3), 1992 September (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 4 (1 of 3), 1992 December (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 4 (2 of 3), 1992 December (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 14 No. 4 (3 of 3), 1992 December (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 1 (1 of 4), 1993 March (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 1 (2 of 4), 1993 March (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 1 (3 of 4), 1993 March (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 1 (4 of 4), 1993 March (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 2 (1 of 4), 1993 June (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 2 (2 of 4), 1993 June (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 2 (3 of 4), 1993 June (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 2 (4 of 4), 1993 June (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 3 (1 of 4), 1993 September (Box 27, Folder 3)